(THUNDER RUMBLING)
MAN:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
It's got to be the Mountain.
He's the biggest.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
He's the strongest.
Bulls are bigger
than lions.\h\h\h\h\h
Doesn't mean I'd\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
pick a bull in a fight.
If the bull had\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
fangs and claws I would.
Right the Mountain
or our man Jaime.\h\h
If he ever gets out.
(THUNDERCLAP)
Loras Tyrell?
Loras Tyrell.\h\h
He's prettier\h\h
than the Queen.
I don't care about pretty.
He's better with a sword\h\h
than any of them.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
How good could he be?
He's been stabbing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Renly Baratheon for years
and Renly ain't dead.\h\h\h\h\h
(LAUGHING)
(HORSE WHINNYING)
The horses seem\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a little spooked to you?
They're horses.
They get spooked by
their own shadows.\h
(SHUSHING)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h (HORSE SNORTING)
Do you hear that?
No.
There's something out there.
(NEIGHING)
(FARTS)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h (GASPS)
(LAUGHING)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h   Oh.
Oh you're\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a right little prick.
You should see your face.
I swear\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
you pissed yourself.
"Oh who goes there? Ahh!"
(LAUGHS)
There is something
out there.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Yeah don't even try me.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h   Rennick.\h\h\h\h
\h
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Rennick!
(RENNICK SCREAMING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
COMMANDER: King in the North!
MEN: The King in the North!
(WATER RUNNING)
(MAN GROANS)
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h  (FLIES BUZZING)
\h
(MAN SCREAMING)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
BOLTON: Five Lannisters dead
for every one of ours.\h\h\h\h\h\h
MAN: They're dead.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Take everything they've got.
BOLTON: We've nowhere to keep
all these prisoners.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Barely enough food
to feed our own.\h\h
We're not executing prisoners
Lord Bolton.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Of course Your Grace.
The officers will
be useful.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Some of them may be privy\h\h
to Tywin Lannister's plans.
I doubt it.
BOLTON: Well\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
we'll learn soon enough.
In my family we say\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
"A naked man has few secrets.
"A flayed man none."
My father outlawed\h\h\h
flaying in the North.
We're not in the North.
We're not torturing them.
The high road's very pretty
but you'll have a hard time
marching your army down it.
The Lannisters hold\h\h\h\h
prisoners of their own.
I won't give them an excuse
to abuse my sisters.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
MAN: No don't!
Don't! Please!\h
(WOMAN SHUSHING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
The rot's set in.
No don't! No don't!
Shh.
Please don't!
It'll get better.\h\h\h\h
It doesn't even hurt.
The rot will spread.
If we don't take\h\h\h\h
the foot now...\h\h\h\h\h
No you can't!
Ser! Please ser.
I can't lose...\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\hYou'll die if she doesn't.
I don't want to be
a cripple please.
Surely one of our men
needs your attention\h
more than this cub.\h\h
Your men are not
my men my lord.
Put this in your\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
mouth and lie down.\h\h\h\h\h
You don't want to watch.
No! You can't!
Bite on it.
It's better than\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
biting your own tongue
believe me.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(SAWING)
What's your name?
Talisa.
Your last name?
You want to know what side
my family fights on?\h\h\h\h\h\h
You know my family name.
You have me at\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a disadvantage.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
That boy lost his foot
on your orders.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
They killed my father.
That boy did?
The family he fights for.
Do you think he's friends
with King Joffrey?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
He's a fisherman's son\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that grew up near Lannisport.
He probably never
held a spear\h\h\h\h\h
before they shoved one
in his hands\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a few months ago.\h\h\h\h\h
I have no hatred
for the lad.\h\h\h\h
(SIGHS)
That should help\h\h\h
his foot grow back.
You'd have us surrender
end all this bloodshed.\h
I understand.\h\h\h\h
The country would
be at peace\h\h\h\h\h\h
and life would be just\h\h
under the righteous hand
of good King Joffrey.\h\h\h
You're going to
kill Joffrey?\h\h
If the gods\h\h\h\h\h\h
give me strength.
And then what?
I don't know.
We'll go back\h
to Winterfell.
I have no desire to\h\h\h\h
sit on the Iron Throne.
So who will?
I don't know.
You're fighting to
overthrow a king\h
and yet you have no plan
for what comes after?\h\h\h
First we have to
win the war.\h\h\h\h
You never told me\h
where you're from.
Volantis.
Volantis?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
You're far from home.
The boy was lucky
you were here.\h\h\h
He was unlucky
that you were.
You're here to answer
for your brother's\h\h\h
latest treasons.\h\h\h\h\h
Your Grace
whatever my traitor
brother has done\h\h
I had no part.\h\h\h\h\h
You know that.\h\h\h\h\h\h
I beg you please...
Ser Lancel\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
tell her of this outrage.
LANCEL:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Using some vile sorcery
your brother fell\h\h\h\h\h\h
on Stafford Lannister\h\h
with an army of wolves.
(CROWD MURMURING)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hThousands of good\h\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hmen were butchered.
After the slaughter\h\h\h
the Northmen feasted on
the flesh of the slain.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Killing you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
would send your\h\h\h
brother a message.
(CRYING)
But my mother insists
on keeping you alive.
Stand.
So we'll have to send\h
your brother a message
some other way.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Meryn.
Leave her face.\h\h\h
I like her pretty.
\h\h\h\h (BLOW LANDS)
\h
(SANSA GASPS)\h\h
(GROANS)
Meryn my lady is
overdressed.\h\h\h\h\h
Unburden her.
If you want Robb\h
Stark to hear us
we're going to\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
have to speak louder.
(SOBBING)
TYRION:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
What is the meaning of this?
What kind of knight\h\h\h
beats a helpless girl?
The kind who\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
serves his king Imp.
Careful now.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
We don't want to get blood
all over your\h\h\h\h\h\h
pretty white cloak.
TYRION: Someone get the girl
something to\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
cover herself with.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
She is to be your queen.
Have you no regard
for her honor?\h\h\h\h
JOFFREY: I'm punishing her.
TYRION: For what crimes?
She did not fight\h\h\h\h
her brother's battle
you half-wit.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
You can't talk\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
to me like that.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
The king can do as he likes!
The Mad King did
as he liked.\h\h\h\h
Has your Uncle\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Jaime ever told you\h\h
what happened to him?
No one threatens His Grace
in the presence\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
of the Kingsguard.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I'm not\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
threatening the king ser.
I am educating my nephew.\h
Bronn the next\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
time Ser Meryn speaks
kill him.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
That was a threat.\h
See the difference?
(CROWD WHISPERING)
I apologize for my
nephew's behavior.
(CROWD MURMURING)
Tell me the truth.\h
Do you want an end\h
to this engagement?
I am loyal to King Joffrey
my one true love.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Lady Stark\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
you may survive us yet.
The little king's
backed up.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Clogged from balls
to brains.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
You think dipping his wick
will cure what ails him?\h\h
There's no cure\h\h
for being a cunt.
But the boy's
at that age.\h
And he's got\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
nothing to do all day\h\h\h\h
but pick wings off flies.
Couldn't hurt to get\h\h\h
some of the poison out.
What are you\h\h\h\h
doing here dog?
Your uncle left\h\h\h\h\h
your nameday present
and asked me to\h\h\h\h\h
see that you got it.
And?
What is it?
Look inside Your Grace.
Your Grace.
Happy nameday
Your Grace.\h\h\h
My nameday has passed.
We won't tell
if you won't.
No.
Her.
Touch her.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Could you hit her?
(LAUGHS)
My uncle sent you?
Yes Your Grace.\h\h\h\h
He chose us himself.
Hmm.
(SLAPPING)\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
Use this.
Harder.
(WHIMPERS)
I said harder.
He'd want me to get
his money's worth.\h
(CRYING)
(SCREAMING)
Your Grace too much pain
will spoil the pleasure.\h
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
Please Your Grace.
Your Grace\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
if your uncle finds out...
Oh I want him to find out.
You will bring her\h\h
to his chambers\h\h\h\h\h
when you're finished
and show him\h\h\h\h\h
what you've done
or the same thing\h\h
will happen to you.
Begin.
(THUDS)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h (WOMAN SCREAMS)
Harder!
Well if it isn't my\h
favorite whoremonger.
Pray I haven't\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
kept you waiting long.
Your Grace.
Now you do\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the Lannisters' bidding
is that it?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Tell me was my\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
brother's body even cold
before you secured\h
your newest patron?
I'm a practical man.
Just not a loyal one.
And who would you\h\h\h
have me be loyal to?
Your brother's corpse?
(CHUCKLES)
I don't like you
Lord Baelish.\h\h\h\h
I don't like your face.
I don't like the words
that come oozing\h\h\h\h\h\h
out of your mouth.\h\h\h\h
I don't want you in my tent
one minute more\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
than necessary.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
So tell me\h\h\h\h\h\h
why are you here?
You can trust Brienne.
Her loyalty comes\h\h\h\h\h
without charge.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
You still have many friends
at court Your Grace\h\h\h\h\h\h
many who believe Ned Stark
erred by not supporting\h\h\h
your claim.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Now I understand.
You know I have the numbers.
You know I'm marching\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
on King's Landing.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
When I take the throne
you hope to retain\h\h\h\h\h
your position.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
And your head.
I would give\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
priority to my head.
I understand that\h
you don't like me
and while that\h\h\h\h\h
saddens me greatly
I did not come here today
seeking your affection.\h\h
When you march\h\h\h\h
on King's Landing
you may find yourself facing
a protracted siege or...\h\h\h\h
open gates.
Your Grace.
Lord Baelish.
All of these tents\h\h
look the same to me.
Would you be so kind...
It would be my pleasure.
It took me weeks
to learn my way\h
around the camp.
Twice I walked in on officers
in stages of undress.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
And the moment I\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
learn which tent is mine
we're on the move again.\h
"Your tent"?
Not "Our tent"?
The king snores perhaps?\h\h
Or simply prefers solitude?
Pressures of command
no doubt.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Four kings vying
for the throne.\h
I am not tutored
in warfare\h\h\h\h\h
but basic arithmetic
favors the side with
the greater numbers.
If war were arithmetic
the mathematicians\h\h\h\h\h
would rule the world.\h\h
I did notice your brother
entering His Grace's\h\h\h\h\h
tent just now.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
The place of a Kingsguard
is by the king's side.\h\h\h
And on the night
of your wedding
who was by\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the king's side then?
You seem quite\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
interested in our marriage.
Your marriage is\h\h
quite interesting.
Not only to me\h\h
but to the realm.
The marriage of a wealthy girl
always breeds interest\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
if nothing else.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
You've never married
have you?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I've been unlucky in\h
my affections sadly.
That is sad.
Though perhaps\h\h\h\h
it's for the best.
The whole notion of marriage
seems to confuse you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
so allow me to explain.
My husband is my king\h\h\h\h
and my king is my husband.
Here is your tent\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Lord Baelish. Good night.
(HOOFBEATS)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
What do you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
know of this place?
Only that the desert\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
around their walls is\h\h\h\h\h\h
called the Garden of Bones.
Every time the Qartheen
shut their gates\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
on a traveler\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the garden grows.
Go on!
You keep moving!
(WOMAN CRYING)
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h (WOMAN SCREAMS)
\h
MAN: Bring her about!\h\h
What kind of fire
melts stone?\h\h\h\h\h
Dragon fire.
There's dragons here?
No all the dragons
are dead.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
What's that smell?
Dead people.
Move.
MAN: Please please no no!
(SCREAMING)
(SOBBING) No.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING STOPS)
\h
(CHAINS RATTLE)\h\h
(HEAVY THUD)
WOMAN: He's dead.
He was my son.
My sister was\h\h
three days ago.
My husband\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the day before that.
They take someone
every day?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Does anyone live?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne.
The Hound.
Joffrey. Cersei.
Ilyn Payne. The Hound.
How dare you?
You may have\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
heard false reports.
You betrayed Ned.
Betrayed?
I wanted him to serve\h\h\h\h\h
as Protector of the Realm.
I begged him to\h\h
seize the moment.
I trusted you.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
My husband trusted you.
And you repaid our\h\h\h
faith with treachery.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h   No my lady.
\h
Get out!\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Cat I've...
I've loved you\h\h\h\h
since I was a boy.
It seems to me that fate\h\h\h
has given us this chance...
Have you lost your mind?
Get out!\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Do you want to see
your girls again?\h
Sansa\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
more beautiful than ever?
And Arya\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
just as wild as ever?
You have Arya too?
Both girls are\h\h\h
healthy and safe.
For now.
But you know the Queen
and you know Joffrey.\h
I fear for their longevity\h\h\h\h
if they remain in the capital.
(KNIFE CLINKS)
What do you want?
The Lannisters will\h
trade your daughters
for the Kingslayer.\h
Of course they will.
Jaime Lannister
for two girls?\h
Robb will never\h\h\h\h\h\h
agree to those terms.
I'm not bringing\h\h\h
these terms to him.
I'm bringing them to you.
You think I keep\h\h\h\h
secrets from my son?
Robb has surprised them all
with his skills in battle\h
but he's not a mother.
Consider it Cat.
You may not get
another chance.
\h\h\h\h   I've brought you a gift.
\h
I don't want your gifts.\h\h\h\h\h\h
A token of Tyrion\h\h\h\h
Lannister's goodwill.
He wants you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
to understand that this
exchange of prisoners\h\h
is offered in good faith.
Good faith?
What's this?
Your husband was\h
an honorable man.
He should rest\h\h\h
beside his family
in the crypts\h\h\h\h\h\h
beneath Winterfell.
\h\h\h\h You may not believe...
\h
Get out.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
(GROANS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
MAN: Get up you dogs!
(WOOD BANGING)
That's him\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the one who picks.
The Mountain.
What are you doing?
He told me he\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
stares at him every day.
That's why he\h\h\h\h\h\h
doesn't get picked.
You.
MAN: Move boy!
Move!
(LIQUID TRICKLING)
TICKLER:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Is there gold and silver
in the village?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I don't know.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h  Gems?
I didn't see any.
Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know.
(RATS SQUEAKING)
TICKLER:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know. Please.
I don't know.
(RAT SQUEAKING)\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h (WHIMPERING)
Which of the villagers
aided them?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I don't know.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h   Who?
I...
Who?
I never saw.
Who?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h I never saw.
Please. Please stop.\h\h\h\h\h\h
Please it's starting to...
Who?
I didn't see\h\h\h\h
anyone help him.
(RAT SHRIEKING)
Take it off!
Who helped him?
Ganes the butcher
and his son.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h That's better.
You've been very helpful.
No stop please!
What are you doing?
Please stop!\h\h\h\h\h\h
Please stop! No! No!
I told you everything! No!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hNo! (SCREAMING)
\h
(RAT CLATTERING)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
ARYA: Joffrey.
Cersei.
Ilyn Payne. The Hound.
WOMAN: Please Polliver.
Some food.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Just a crust of bread.
(WOMAN CRYING)
Polliver.
The Mountain.
STANNIS:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Lady Stark I had not thought\h
to find you in the Stormlands.
I had not thought to\h\h
be here Lord Stannis.
Can that truly be you?
Who else might it be?
When I saw your standard
I couldn't be sure.\h\h\h\h\h\h
Whose banner is that?
\h
\h\h\h\h My own.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I suppose if we\h\h\h
used the same one
the battle would be
terribly confusing.
Why is your stag on fire?
The king has\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
taken for his sigil
the fiery heart of
the Lord of Light.
Ah you must be\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
this fire priestess\h\h\h
we hear so much about.
Mmm brother
now I understand\h\h\h\h\h\h
why you found religion
in your old age.\h\h\h\h\h\h
Watch yourself Renly.
RENLY: No no
I'm relieved.\h
I never really believed
you were a fanatic.\h\h\h\h
Charmless rigid
a bore yes\h\h\h\h\h
but not a godly man.
You should kneel\h\h\h\h
before your brother.
He's the Lord's chosen
born amidst salt and smoke.
Born amidst salt and smoke?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h   Is he a ham?
\h
STANNIS: That's twice\h\h\h\h\h
I've warned you.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Listen to yourselves.
If you were sons of mine
I would knock\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
your heads together\h\h\h\h\h\h
and lock you in a bedchamber
until you remembered\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that you were brothers.\h\h\h\h\h
It is strange to find you
beside my brother\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Lady Stark.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Your husband was\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a supporter of my claim.
Lord Eddard's integrity
cost him his head.\h\h\h\h\h
And you sit\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
beside this pretender
and chastise me.\h\h\h\h\h
We share a common enemy.
The Iron Throne\h\h
is mine by right.
All those that\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
deny that are my foes.
The whole realm denies it
from Dorne to the Wall.\h\h\h
Old men deny it\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
with their death rattle
and unborn children deny it
in their mother's wombs.\h\h\h
No one wants you
for their king.\h
You never wanted\h\h\h\h\h
any friends brother.
But a man without friends
is a man without power.\h\h
For the sake of\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the mother who bore us
I will give you this\h\h\h\h
one night to reconsider.
Strike your banners\h\h\h
come to me before dawn
and I will grant you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
your old seat in the Council.
I'll even name you my heir
until a son is born to me.
Otherwise I shall
destroy you.\h\h\h\h\h
Look across those fields
brother.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Can you see\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
all those banners?
You think a few bolts of cloth
will make you king?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
RENLY: No.
The men holding\h\h\h\h\h
those bolts of cloth
will make me king.\h\h
We shall see Renly.
Come the dawn we shall see.
Look to your sins
Lord Renly.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
The night is dark\h\h\h
and full of terrors.
Would you believe
I loved him once?
I thought we were welcome.
If you heard a Dothraki horde
was approaching your city\h\h\h
you might do the same
Khaleesi.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Horde?
My name is Daenerys...
Daenerys Stormborn of
the house Targaryen.\h
You know me my lord?
Only by reputation
Khaleesi.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
And I'm no lord\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
merely a humble merchant.
They call you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the Mother of Dragons.
And what should
I call you?\h\h\h\h
Oh my name is quite long
and quite impossible\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
for foreigners to pronounce.
I am simply\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a trader of spices.
But we are the Thirteen
charged with the governance
and protection of Qarth\h\h\h
the greatest city\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that ever was or will be.
The beauty of\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Quarth is legendary...
\h
\h\h\h\hQarth.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Qarth.
Might we see the dragons?
My friend
we have traveled very far.
We have no food no water.
Once I see my people fed
I would be honored...\h\h\h\h
Forgive me\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Mother of Dragons
but no man alive has\h
seen a living dragon.
Some of my more\h\h
skeptical friends
refuse to believe
your children\h\h\h\h
even exist.
All we ask is the chance
to see for ourselves.\h\h\h
I am not a liar.
Oh I don't think you are.
But as I've\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
never met you before
my opinion on the matter
is of limited value.\h\h\h\h
Where I come from
guests are\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
treated with respect\h\h\h\h\h
not insulted at the gates.
Then perhaps you should\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
return to where you come from.
We wish you well.
What are you doing?
You promised to receive me.
We have received you.
Here we are\h\h\h\h\h
and here you are.
If you do not let us in
all of us will die.\h\h\h\h\h
Which we shall
deeply regret.
But Qarth did not become
the greatest city\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that ever was or will be
by letting Dothraki savages
through its gates.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Khaleesi please be careful.
Thirteen!
When my dragons are grown
we will take back\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
what was stolen from me\h\h\h
and destroy those\h\h\h
who have wronged me.
We will lay waste to armies\h\h\h
and burn cities to the ground.
Turn us away and we\h
will burn you first.
Ah.
You are a true Targaryen.
Only as you said
a moment ago\h\h\h\h
if we don't let\h\h\h
you into the city
you will all die.\h
And so...
Retreating in fear
from a little girl
is unbecoming of\h
the greatest city
that ever was or will be.
The discussion is over
Xaro Xhoan Daxos.\h\h\h\h\h\h
The Thirteen have spoken.
I am one of the Thirteen
and I am still speaking.
The girl threatens
to burn our city\h\h
to the ground\h\h\h\h\h
and you would invite her in
for a cup of wine?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
She is\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the Mother of Dragons.
Do you expect her to\h\h\h
watch her people starve
without breathing fire?
I believe we can\h\h\h\h
allow a few Dothraki
through our gates\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
without dooming our city.
After all here I am
a savage from\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the Summer Isles\h\h\h\h\h\h
and Qarth still stands.
Our decision is final.
Very well.
I invoke soumai.
I will vouch for her
her people\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
and her dragons\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
in accordance with the law.
Be it on your head.
Welcome to Qarth
my lady.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
MOUNTAIN: You.
TICKLER:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Is there gold or silver
in the village?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I'm not from the village.
Where is the Brotherhood?
I don't know\h
what that is.
(SQUEAKING)
(HORSES NEIGH)
MAN: You two.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Take Lord Lannister's\h\h
things to his quarters.
What's this?
We weren't expecting you\h\h
till tomorrow Lord Tywin.
(CHUCKLES) Evidently not.
Why are\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
these prisoners not
in their cells?\h\h\h\h
MOUNTAIN: Cells are\h\h
overflowing my lord.
POLLIVER:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
This lot won't be here long.\h\h
Don't need no permanent place.
After we interrogate 'em
we usually just...\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Are we so well-manned\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that we can afford to discard
able young bodies\h\h\h\h
and skilled laborers?
You do you have a trade?
GENDRY: Smith my lord.
What are you looking at?
Kneel!\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Kneel or I'll carve\h
your lungs out boy.
He'll do no such thing.
This one's a girl
you idiot\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
dressed as a boy.
Why?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
Safer to travel
my lord.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Smart.
More than I can\h\h
say for this lot.
Get these prisoners to work.
Bring the girl.
I need a new cupbearer.
MOUNTAIN: My lord.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Your visits are\h
too few cousin.
Her Grace\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the Queen Regent
commands you to release
Grand Maester Pycelle.\h
Here's your warrant.
So it is.
Will you take a cup with me?
I find that mulled\h\h
wine helps me sleep.
I am here at\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Her Grace's behest\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
not to drink with you Imp.
If my sister was so\h\h\h
concerned for Pycelle
I would have thought
she'd come herself.\h
Instead she sends you.\h\h\h\h
What am I to make of that?
I don't care\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
what you make of it
so long as you release\h\h\h\h
your prisoner immediately.
And you've received\h\h
these instructions\h\h\h
directly from Cersei?
As I said several times.
And you've waited this long
to deliver the information?
When the Queen Regent\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
gives me a command\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I carry it out without delay.
Cersei must have\h\h\h
great trust in you
allowing you into her chamber
during the hour of the wolf.\h
The Queen Regent has\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
a great many responsibilities.
She often works\h\h\h\h\h
from dusk till dawn.
She must be very glad\h\h
to have you helping her
from dusk till dawn.\h\h\h
Ah.
Lavender oil.
She always loved\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
lavender oil even as a girl.
I am a knight!
An anointed knight yes.
Tell me\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
did Cersei have
you knighted\h\h\h
before or after she\h\h\h
took you into her bed?
What? Nothing to say?
No more warnings
for me ser?\h\h\h\h
You will withdraw\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
these filthy accusations.
Have you ever\h\h\h\h
given any thought
to what King Joffrey
will have to say\h\h\h\h
when he finds out\h\h
you've been bedding
his mother?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
It's not my fault!
Did she take you\h\h
against your will?
Can you not defend yourself
knight?\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Your own father Lord Tywin
when I was named\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
the King's squire\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
he told me to obey
her in everything.
Did he tell you\h\h
to fuck her too?
I only meant I\h\h\h
did as I was bid.
Hated every moment of it
is that what\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
you'll have me believe?
A high place in court
a knighthood\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
my sister's legs spreading
open for you at night.\h\h\h\h
Oh yes\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
it must have been terrible.
Wait here. His Grace\h\h\h
will want to hear this.
Mercy! Mercy\h\h\h\h\h\h
my lord! I beg you.
Save it for Joffrey.\h\h\h
He loves a good grovel.
My lord it was\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
your sister's bidding
the Queen.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
I'll leave the city
at once I swear.\h\h
No I think not.
My lord?
You heard me.
My father told you
to obey my sister.
Obey her.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Stay close to her side.
Keep her trust.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Pleasure her\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
whenever she requires.
No one ever need know
as long as you\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
keep faith with me.\h\h\h
I want to know\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
what Cersei is doing
where she goes who she sees\h
what they talk of everything.
And you will tell me.
Yes my lord I will.
I swear it as you command.
Oh rise rise.
Let us drink to\h\h\h
our understanding.
Oh you don't have a cup.
Oh well.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Smile cousin. My sister
is a beautiful woman\h\h\h
and it's all for\h\h\h\h\h\h
the good of the realm.
Go back and tell her\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that I beg her forgiveness
that I want no more
conflict between us
and that henceforth
I shall do nothing\h\h\h
without her consent.\h
But her demands?
Oh I'll give her Pycelle.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h You will?
\h
Yes I'll release him\h\h\h\h
in the morning.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Cersei can keep him\h\h\h\h
as a pet if she wants
but I will not have
him on the Council.
I could swear\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
that I had not harmed\h\h\h\h\h
a single hair on his head
but that would not\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
strictly speaking be true.
(WOOD CREAKING)
MAN:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Stay within one table length.
Your Grace.
Do your knucklebones
bring you luck?\h\h\h\h\h
Well life's been good
since you hacked\h\h\h\h\h\h
them off Your Grace.\h
And it's four less\h\h\h
fingernails to clean.
Fewer.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h Pardon?
Four fewer\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
fingernails to clean.
Never understood why\h
you had to wear them.
It reminds me of\h\h\h
where I come from\h\h
and where I am now.
It reminds me\h\h\h
of your justice.
It was an honest punishment
and you were good\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
with the cleaver.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
You were a hero
and a smuggler.
A good act does\h\h\h\h\h\h
not wash out the bad
nor a bad the good.\h\h
A lesson I've tried
to teach my son.\h\h\h
Does he listen?
To me?
Gods no.
But if your red woman\h\h
told him to leap\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
from the crow's nest...
She has a name.
I trust you've not forgotten
your smuggler's tricks.\h\h\h\h\h
I've lived within
the law for 17...
I want you to be\h\h\h\h\h
a smuggler this time.
Any shore any night.
What am I bringing ashore?
The red woman.
No one must know\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
what you do and we'll not
speak of this again.\h\h\h\h\h
I am true to Your Grace
and always will be\h\h\h\h
but surely there are\h\h\h\h\h
other ways cleaner ways.
Cleaner ways don't
win wars.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Are you afraid
Onion Knight?\h\h
Someone once told me
the night is dark\h\h\h
and full of terrors.
You've carried\h\h\h\h\h
more unpleasant\h\h\h\h
cargo in your time.
Are you a good man
Ser Davos Seaworth?
I'd say my parts\h\h\h
are mixed my lady
good and bad.\h\h\h\h\h\h
If half an onion\h\h\h\h
is black with rot\h\h
it's a rotten onion.
A man is good\h
or he is evil.
And which are you?\h\h\h\h\h
\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h  Oh good.
I'm a knight myself of sorts
a champion of light and life.\h
Well that must be
very nice for you.
Do you love your wife?
\h
I do.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Yet you have\h\h\h\h\h\h
known other women.
Don't talk about my wife.
I'm not. I'm talking
about other women.\h\h
Like me Ser Davos.
You want me.
You want to see\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
what's beneath this robe.
And you will.
Strange that\h\h\h\h\h\h
this Lord of Light
asks you to work
in the shadows.\h
Shadows cannot live\h\h\h\h
in the dark Ser Davos.
They are servants of light
the children of fire.\h\h\h\h\h\h
And the brighter the flame
the darker they are.\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
These weren't here before.\h
They've barred the passage.
They can't bar
our passage.\h\h
Gods protect us.
There's only one god
Ser Davos\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
and he only protects
those who serve him.
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
(MOANING)
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(SHRIEKING)
(GROWLS)